Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 3: Boxes 45-66
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 3: Boxes 45-66
- Box: 57, Folder: 4 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Item 14: Relations Reviews: News and Views for Management, Publication (Box 57, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. no.69-33 (1969:Oct. 6). Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Relations Reviews: News and Views for Management, Publication (Box 57, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. no.69-34 (1969:Oct. 13). Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Relations Reviews: News and Views for Management, Publication (Box 57, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. no.69-35 (1969:Oct. 20). Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Relations Reviews: Strike Extra, Publication (Box 57, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. no.69-35X (1969:Oct. 29). Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Relations Reviews: Strike Extra, Publication (Box 57, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. no.69-35X2 (1969:Nov. 3). Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Relations Reviews: Strike Extra, Publication (Box 57, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. no.69-35X3 (1969:Nov. 6). Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Employee Relations News: a commentary for General Electric Management by Employee Relations Service, Publication (Box 57, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. no.64-48 (1964:Dec. 21). Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Employee Relations News: a commentary for General Electric Management by Employee Relations Service, Publication (Box 57, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. no.67-21 (1967:Sep. 25). Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Employee Relations News: a commentary for General Electric Management by Employee Relations Service, Publication (Box 57, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. no.67-20 (1967:Sep. 11). Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Employee Relations News: a commentary for General Electric Management by Employee Relations Service, Publication (Box 57, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. no.67-19 (1967:Aug. 14). Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Employee Relations News: a commentary for General Electric Management by Employee Relations Service, Publication (Box 57, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. no.67-18 (1967:July 24). Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Employee Relations News: a commentary for General Electric Management by Employee Relations Service, Publication (Box 57, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. no.67-17 (1967:July 10). Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Employee Relations News: a commentary for General Electric Management by Employee Relations Service, Publication (Box 57, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. no.67-16 (1967:June 19). Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Employee Relations News: a commentary for General Electric Management by Employee Relations Service, Publication (Box 57, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. no.67-14 (1967:May 15). Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Employee Relations News: a commentary for General Electric Management by Employee Relations Service, Publication (Box 57, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. no.67-13 (1967:Apr. 24). Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Employee Relations News: a commentary for General Electric Management by Employee Relations Service, Publication (Box 57, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. no.67-12 (1967:Apr. 10). Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Employee Relations News: a commentary for General Electric Management by Employee Relations Service, Publication (Box 57, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. no.67-11 (1967:Mar. 20). Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Employee Relations News: a commentary for General Electric Management by Employee Relations Service, Publication (Box 57, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. no.67-10 (1967:Mar. 13). Item is in English.
  - Item 32: Employee Relations News: a commentary for General Electric Management by Employee Relations Service, Publication (Box 57, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. no.67-9 (1967:Mar. 6). Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Employee Relations News: a commentary for General Electric Management by Employee Relations Service, Publication (Box 57, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. no.67-8 (1967:Feb. 27). Item is in English.
  - Item 34: Employee Relations News: a commentary for General Electric Management by Employee Relations Service, Publication (Box 57, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. no.67-7 (1967:Feb. 20). Item is in English.
  - Item 35: Employee Relations News: a commentary for General Electric Management by Employee Relations Service, Publication (Box 57, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. no.67-6 (1967:Feb. 13). Item is in English.
  - Item 36: Employee Relations News: a commentary for General Electric Management by Employee Relations Service, Publication (Box 57, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. no.67-5 (1967:Feb. 6). Item is in English.
  - Item 37: Employee Relations News: a commentary for General Electric Management by Employee Relations Service, Publication (Box 57, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. no.67-4 (1967:Jan. 30). Item is in English.
  - Item 38: Employee Relations News: a commentary for General Electric Management by Employee Relations Service, Publication (Box 57, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. no.67-3 (1967:Jan. 23). Item is in English.
  - Item 39: Employee Relations News: a commentary for General Electric Management by Employee Relations Service, Publication (Box 57, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. no.67-2 (1967:Jan. 16). Item is in English.
  - Item 40: Employee Relations News: a commentary for General Electric Management by Employee Relations Service, Publication (Box 57, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. no.67-1 (1967:Jan. 9). Item is in English.
  - Item 41: Supervisor's Guide to General Electric Job Information, Publication (Box 57, Folder 4)
    By Ralph L. Lee. handbook. Item is in English.
- Box: 57, Folder: 5 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Organizational changes designed to strengthen General Electric's corporate staff work, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By N. Herington. Sept 18, Press release. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Employee Relations News: a commentary for General Electric Management by Employee Relations Service, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. no.68-14 (1968:Apr. 29). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Employee Relations News: a commentary for General Electric Management by Employee Relations Service, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. no.68-30 (1968:Dec. 9). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Employee Relations News: a commentary for General Electric Management by Employee Relations Service, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. no.68-18 (1968:May 27). Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Employee Relations News: a commentary for General Electric Management by Employee Relations Service, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. no.68-17 (1968:May 20). Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Employee Relations News: a commentary for General Electric Management by Employee Relations Service, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. no.68-16 (1968:May 13). Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Employee Relations News: a commentary for General Electric Management by Employee Relations Service, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. no.68-15 (1968:May 6). Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Employee Relations News: a commentary for General Electric Management by Employee Relations Service, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. no.98-19 (1968:June 17). Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Employee Relations News: a commentary for General Electric Management by Employee Relations Service, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. no.68-20 (1968:July 1). Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Employee Relations News: a commentary for General Electric Management by Employee Relations Service, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. no.68-21 (1968:July 15). Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Employee Relations News: a commentary for General Electric Management by Employee Relations Service, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. no.68-23 (1968:Aug. 19). Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Employee Relations News: a commentary for General Electric Management by Employee Relations Service, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. no.68-24 (1968:Sep. 9). Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Employee Relations News: a commentary for General Electric Management by Employee Relations Service, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. no.68-25 (1968:Sep. 23). Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Employee Relations News: a commentary for General Electric Management by Employee Relations Service, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. no.68-26 (1968:Oct. 7). Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Union Representatives Pension Plan, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. Effective January 26, 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Community and Government Relations Bulletin: For Circulation Among General Electric Managers, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By Community and Government Relations. no.67-1 (1967:Oct. 13). Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Community and Government Relations Bulletin: For Circulation Among General Electric Managers, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By Community and Government Relations Service, General Electric Company. no.64-3 (1964:Apr. 17). Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Suggested Community Activities in Which Both Large and Small Employers Can Participate at Little or no Cost, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By Plant Community Relations Department. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: A letter to Sales and Service People on the outlook for 1966 negotiations, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By General Electric Marketing and Public Relations Services; J. Stanford Smith. July 12, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Louisbille Plan: A Case History of Genral Electric's Entry Into Louisville, Kentucky, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By General Electric Company Employee and Plant Communitye Relations. November, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Employee Relations News, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By Employee Relations Service. no.68-5 (1968: Feb. 12). Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Employee Relations News, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By General Electric Company Employee Relations Services. no.68-4 (1968:Feb. 5). Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Employee Relations News, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By General Electric Company Employee Relations Services. no.68-13 (1968:Apr. 22). Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Employee Relations News, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By General Electric Company Employee Relations Services. no.67-27 (1968:Dec. 18). Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Employee Relations News, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By General Electric Company Employee Relations Services. no.67-22 (1968:Oct. 9). Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Employee Relations News, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By General Electric Company Employee Relations Services. no.67-26 (1968:Dec. 4). Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Employee Relations News, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By General Electric Company Employee Relations Services. no.67-23 (1968:Oct. 23). Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Employment and Unemployment - in the U.S. Economy - In General Electric, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By Relations Services. August 11, 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: The Jobless: What Business Can Do, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By Laurence I. Wood. Address before the Instiute on "The Great Society of the Jobless", International Association of Personnel in Employment Security and the Division of Social Sciences of Howard University, Washington, DC, April 13, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: The Erie Story: A Case History of a Successful Community Telivision Series, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By Employee and Plant Community Relations. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: The Monogram, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. v.16:no.6 (1967:Aug./Sep.). Item is in English.
  - Item 32: Index to Public and Employee Relations Services Printed Materials, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By General Electric Public and Employee Relations Services. October, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 33: A Yardstick to Better Government for You, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By Plant Community Relations Department. 12-54. Item is in English.
  - Item 34: Suggestion Plan, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By Plant Community Relations Department. 4-55. Item is in English.
  - Item 35: Employees Annual Suggestion Report, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By Large Motor and Generator Department General Electric. Jan1, 1954 - Dec. 31, 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 36: Suggested Community Activities in Which Both Large and Small Employers Can Participate at Little or no Cost, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 37: Plant Community Relations Review: GE Aims to Be a Good Corporate Citizen, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. v.2:no.10 (1953:Oct.). Item is in English.
  - Item 38: Employee and Plant Community Relations Information Letter, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By J. T. McCarty. no.21 (1953:Mar. 19). Item is in English.
  - Item 39: Cover Letter for the Cumulative Report of the GE Corporate Alumnus Program, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By J. Moreau Brown. May 26, 1961. Item is in English.
  - Item 40: Relations Reviews: Strike Extra, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. no.69-35X5 (1969:Nov. 13). Item is in English.
  - Item 41: Relations Reviews: Strike Extra, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. no.69-35X6 (1969:Nov. 17). Item is in English.
  - Item 42: Relations Reviews: Strike Extra, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. no.69-35X7 (1969:Nov. 24). Item is in English.
  - Item 43: Relations Reviews: Strike Extra, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. no.69-35X8 (1969:Dec. 5). Item is in English.
  - Item 44: Relations Reviews: Strike Extra, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. no.69-35X9 (1969:Dec. 9). Item is in English.
  - Item 45: Relations Reviews: Strike Extra, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. no.69-35X10 (1969:Dec. 11). Item is in English.
  - Item 46: Relations Reviews: Strike Extra, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. no.69-35X11 (1969:Dec. 15). Item is in English.
  - Item 47: Relations Reviews: Strike Extra, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. no.69-35X12 (1969:Dec. 17). Item is in English.
  - Item 48: Relations Reviews: Strike Extra, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. no.69-35X13 (1969:Dec. 22). Item is in English.
  - Item 49: Relations Reviews: Strike Extra, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. no.69-35X14 (1969:Dec. 31). Item is in English.
  - Item 50: Relations Reviews: Strike Extra, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. no.70-X (1970:Jan. 8). Item is in English.
  - Item 51: Relations Reviews: Strike Extra, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. no.70-X2 (1970:Jan. 12). Item is in English.
  - Item 52: Relations Reviews: Strike Extra, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. no.70-X3 (1970:Jan. 15). Item is in English.
  - Item 53: Relations Reviews: Strike Extra, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. no.70-X4 (1970:Jan. 19). Item is in English.
  - Item 54: Relations Reviews: Strike Extra, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. no.70-X5 (1970:Jan. 21). Item is in English.
  - Item 55: Relations Reviews: Strike Extra, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. no.70-X6 (1970:Jan. 26). Item is in English.
  - Item 56: Relations Reviews: Strike Extra, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. no.70-X7 (1970:Feb. 2). Item is in English.
  - Item 57: Relations Reviews, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. no.70-1 (1970:Feb. 9). Item is in English.
  - Item 58: Relations Reviews, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. no.70-2 (1970:Feb. 16). Item is in English.
  - Item 59: Relations Reviews, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. no.70-3 (1970:Feb. 23). Item is in English.
  - Item 60: Relations Reviews, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. no.70-4 (1970:Mar. 9). Item is in English.
  - Item 61: Relations Reviews, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. no.70-5 (1970:Mar. 23). Item is in English.
  - Item 62: How a good business climate benefits all citizens, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. Share Owners Quarterly, October 25, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 63: Relations News Letter, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. December 19, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 64: Employee Relations News, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. no.67-15 (1967:June 5). Item is in English.
  - Item 65: The General Electric Lockland Plan: A Case History of a Planned Community Advertising Program, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. October 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 66: Crisis of the Cities: A Corporate Concern, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By Gerald L. Phillippe. Address before the Annual Meeting of the U.S. Chamber of Commerce, Washington, DC, May 1, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 67: At Work in Industry Today, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By Gerald L. Phillippe. 50 case reports on Negroes at work in the General Electric Company. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 68: Motion Pictures and Slidefilms, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Item 69: Relations Reviews: Strike Extra, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. no.69-35X6 (1969:Nov. 17). Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 70: Idea Exchange on Solving Urban Problems Cover Letter, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By E. J. Kneeland. October 18, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 71: Plant Community Relations Literature, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Item 72: To Readers of the Labor Policy and Practice Bulletin, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By L. R. Boulware. May 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 73: Relations Reviews: Strike Extra, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. no.69-35X5 (1969:Nov. 13). Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 74: Idea Exchange on Solving Urban Problems, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    By Employee Communication Operation of Employee Relations. Item is in English.
- Box: 57, Folder: 6 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Relations News Letter, Publication (Box 57, Folder 6)
    By General Electric. June 26, 1963. Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Developing Trends and Changing Institutions: Our Future Business Environment, Publication (Box 57, Folder 6)
    By General Electric. April, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Community and Government Relations Bulletin: For Circulation Among General Electric Managers, Publication (Box 57, Folder 6)
    By General Electric. no.64-4 (1964:Sep. 17). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Freedom We Fight For, Publication (Box 57, Folder 6)
    By General Electric. February 16, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Monogram, Publication (Box 57, Folder 6)
    By General Electric. 1967/1968 Campus digest edition. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Automation in General Electric: The Human Side of the Story, Publication (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Community and Government Relations Bulletin: For Circulation Among General Electric Managers, Publication (Box 57, Folder 6)
    By General Electric. no.64-6 (1964:Nov. 13). Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Technology and the Pollution Problem, Publication (Box 57, Folder 6)
    By Arthur M. Bueche. Testimony before the Subcommittee on Science, Research and Development on "The Adequacy of Technology for Pollution Abatement." U.S. House of Representatives, Washington, DC, August 9, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Technology and the Pollution Problem, Publication (Box 57, Folder 6)
    By Arthur M. Bueche. Testimony before the Subcommittee on Science, Research and Development on "The Adequacy of Technology for Pollution Abatement." U.S. House of Representatives, Washington, DC, August 9, 1966. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Technology and the Pollution Problem, Publication (Box 57, Folder 6)
    By Arthur M. Bueche. Testimony before the Subcommittee on Science, Research and Development on "The Adequacy of Technology for Pollution Abatement." U.S. House of Representatives, Washington, DC, August 9, 1966. Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Maturing Phase of World Trade, Publication (Box 57, Folder 6)
    By Fred J. Borch. Address before the National Foreign Trade Council, New York, NY, November 2, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Maturing Phase of World Trade, Publication (Box 57, Folder 6)
    By Fred J. Borch. Address before the National Foreign Trade Council, New York, NY, November 2, 1966. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The Maturing Phase of World Trade, Publication (Box 57, Folder 6)
    By Fred J. Borch. Address before the National Foreign Trade Council, New York, NY, November 2, 1966. Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Publication List for Universities, Publication (Box 57, Folder 6)
    By General Electric. Academic Year 1966/1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Community and Government Relations Bulletin: For Circulation Among General Electric Managers, Publication (Box 57, Folder 6)
    By General Electric. no.64-3 (1964:Apr. 17). Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Letter to Mr. Ray Ross, Regional Director, UAW-CIO, Publication (Box 57, Folder 6)
    By L. R. Boulware. April 25, 1955. Correspondence. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Chapter Seven: Communication and Conflict, Publication (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Item 18: Dear President:, Publication (Box 57, Folder 6)
    By J. Moreau Brown. May 26, 1961. Correspondence. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Community and Government Relations Bulletin: For Circulation Among General Electric Managers, Publication (Box 57, Folder 6)
    By Fred J. Borch. no.64-4 (1964:Sep. 17). Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Constructive Citizenship, Publication (Box 57, Folder 6)
    By General Electric. Pamphlet. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Constructive Citizenship, Publication (Box 57, Folder 6)
    By General Electric. Pamphlet. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Our Common Cause in World Competition, Publication (Box 57, Folder 6)
    By Fred J. Borch. An address before the Economic Club of New York. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Our Common Cause in World Competition, Publication (Box 57, Folder 6)
    By Fred J. Borch. An address before the Economic Club of New York. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Employment and Unemployment in the U.S. Economy, in General Electric, Publication (Box 57, Folder 6)
    By General Electric. August 11, 1960. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Community and Government Relations Bulletin: For Circulation Among General Electric Managers, Publication (Box 57, Folder 6)
    By General Electric. no.64-3 (1964:Apr. 17). Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Relations News Letter, Publication (Box 57, Folder 6)
    By General Electric. September 21, 1966. Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Relations News Letter, Publication (Box 57, Folder 6)
    By General Electric. September 6, 1966. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Relations News Letter, Publication (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Item 29: Relations Reviews, Publication (Box 57, Folder 6)
    By General Electric. no.70-6 (1970:Apr. 6). Item is in English.